Do as I say later.
Hit me harder.
Do you think Lu Ye will come to save you?
No one knows Lu Ye better than I do.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 2]
Young Master.
Has Shen Tianbai really lost his memory?
I don't know.
He...
has always been long‑suffering.
Why don't we just kill him?
That will settle it once and for all.
The old man's death
hasn't been fully investigated yet.
He is still useful.
Besides,
killing him this way
is letting him off too easily.
Should we continue the torture then?
Tomorrow,
we'll play a different game.
[Lu Mansion]
Why?
You can't even stand for an hour?
You're not fit to serve me.
Leave.
I can learn.
Young Master, be careful.
Don't get yourself hurt.
Do you really want
to stay by my side that much?
Yes.
Why?
To repay your kindness?
I don't need that.
I'm scared.
You're the only person I know.
Don't send me away.
Officer Shen.
Shen Tianbai,
what exactly are you up to?
Forget it.
This tastes awful.
This is for you.
You used to love peanut butter the most.
Lu Ye,
you're testing me.
In the past,
were we close?
Not really.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
You are severely allergic to peanuts.
Did you even forget that?
You...
lied to me.
I was bored,
so I was just teasing you.
You're about to die.
Still can't remember?
I really...
I really don't remember anything,
Young Master.
Seems you don't want me to die.
I believe you.
If you want to make a living by my side,
loyalty alone is not enough.
You also have to be useful.
Kill him.
Who is he?
Does it matter?
He's just a traitor.
I almost forgot.
To Officer Shen,
it is indeed very important.
After all, Officer Shen
is the savior of our Ningcheng.
How could he kill the innocent?
What about you,
Shen Tianbai?
Is right and wrong
just as important to you?
It's time for you to taste
what it's like to be trampled underfoot.
It's Biao.
Lu Ye,
you still don't believe me.
A scumbag who collects
blood money at the docks
wouldn't be an innocent victim.
Young Master,
you misunderstood.
I just wanted to know how he offended you.
That way...
I can find the most suitable way
for him to die.
Young Master,
is that enough?
Come here.
Yes.
You did such a good job.
You deserve a reward.
Hurry up and follow.
Damn it.
That unreliable guy, Biao,
was supposed to pick up
this batch of goods at Xingang.
Where is he?
He must have gone drinking again.
Damn it, who is it?
Long time no see.
Young...
Young Master.
The Qingtian Gang has fallen.
I heard you've been having a hard time,
shining shoes for a few coppers.
But I don't need my shoes shined.
Get lost.
I'm telling you,
get the hell out of here.
Don't get in the way of my business,
or I won't spare you.
Business?
You mean stealing my goods
to sell for money?
Your goods?
Nonsense!
Finders keepers.
Don't run if you have the guts.
We'll talk when Biao gets here.
He's already here.
What?
You...
Freeze.
Officer Shen,
you're still highly skilled
even with amnesia.
Make a choice:
the goods
or your life?
My life.
My life, Young Master.
Young Master, please spare me.
I'll go get the goods for you right now.
Lu Ye, prepare to die!
Young Master, watch out!
Young Master,
are you okay?
Shen Tianbai,
you actually took a stab for me.
Water.
Open your mouth.
It's hot.
You're being picky.
Drink it or leave it.
Young Master.
Young Master, you're fine.
Great.
You talk too much
for someone about to die.
Save your words
for your journey to the afterlife.
Lu Ye,
you still refuse to believe me.
Oh no.
But
as long as you're fine.
Young Master,
how could you risk your life
just to test Shen Tianbai?
That driver is a madman—
Alright, Uncle Zhong.
Don't worry.
I'm perfectly fine,
and I brought the goods back.
By the way,
at the police station,
I had an informant
check the autopsy report.
Besides the shot from Shen Tianbai,
there was also a slow-acting poison
in the old chief's body.
Poison?
Do you think this poison could also
be related to Shen Tianbai?
No.
If Shen Tianbai wanted to kill someone,
he wouldn't hide it.
He wouldn't stoop to
such underhanded methods.
Besides the shot, there was poison.
You can guard against outsiders
day and night,
but it's hard
to guard against a thief within.
Are you saying
there's a mole in the Qingtian Gang?
How is the investigation
into Shen Tianbai going?
Shen Tianbai didn't disappear
for no reason.
He was kicked out of the police force.
What?
Who did it?
His master, Wu Ren.
Shen Tianbai was cultivated
by Wu Ren himself.
How is that possible?
It's said that these years,
Shen Tianbai was too prominent
and blocked Wu Ren's path to promotion.
So Wu Ren wanted to take the opportunity
to get rid of Shen Tianbai.
Moreover,
there was indeed a fire
at the train station that day,
which matches what Shen Tianbai said.
Shen Tianbai,
what exactly happened that night?
Why did you fire that shot?
Officer Shen, you're really capable.
You can even thrive in your rival's house.
[Hui, Shisha Gang]
Impressive, really.
Hui, just speak your mind.
I heard
you helped Lu Ye steal
a shipment from Qinglong.
Shen Tianbai,
you haven't forgotten why you
joined the Qingtian Gang, have you?
Of course.
There's a mole in the Qingtian Gang.
Thanks to him,
your Shisha Gang
was able to get rid of Lu Wenbiao.
However,
when the deal was over,
even you didn't know
who this person really was.
I joined the Qingtian Gang
for one purpose,
which is to find the mole
and kill him first.
Lu Ye wants to catch the mole.
So do I.
At least, our goals are the same for now.
To gain his trust,
of course, I have to help him
get that shipment.
Very well.
As expected of you, Officer Shen.
If it weren't for your good master,
[Shen Tianbai Unaccounted‑For: Wu Ren,
Hero's Master, Takes Over Police Affairs]
who would have thought
we'd be buddies one day?
Master.
Is he even worthy?